// list array will all questions and answers for the trivia questions
const qaArray = [
  {
    question:
      "Who teaches Mowgli about 'The Bare Necessities' in the Jungle Book?",
    answer: "Baloo",
    options: ["Baloo", "Bagheera", "Shere Khan", "Kaa"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Disney's Animal Kingdom theme park opened in Florida in which year?",
    answer: "1998",
    options: ["1995", "1996", "1997", "1998"],
  },
  {
    question: "Gaston is the villain in which Disney movie?",
    answer: "Beauty and the Beast",
    options: [
      "Cinderella",
      "Beauty and the Beast",
      "Snow White",
      "Sleeping Beauty",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the family in Mary Poppins?",
    answer: "Banks",
    options: ["Banks", "Smith", "Johnson", "Brown"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of Buzz and Woody's original owner in Toy Story?",
    answer: "Andy",
    options: ["Andy", "Molly", "Sid", "Bonnie"],
  },
  {
    question: "Let it Go' is a song from which famous Disney animated movie?",
    answer: "Frozen",
    options: ["Frozen", "Tangled", "Moana", "Brave"],
  },
  {
    question: "Nemo ends up in a tank in which sort of office?",
    answer: "Dentist",
    options: ["Veterinarian", "Doctor", "Dentist", "Lawyer"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "What type of animal was Robin in the animated version of Robin Hood?",
    answer: "Fox",
    options: ["Bear", "Fox", "Lion", "Rabbit"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Disney opened its first European park close to which city in 1992?",
    answer: "Paris",
    options: ["London", "Berlin", "Madrid", "Paris"],
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the wisecracking genie in 'Aladdin'?",
    answer: "Genie",
    options: ["Genie", "Jafar", "Abu", "Iago"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which Disney character is a talking candlestick in 'Beauty and the Beast'?",
    answer: "Lumière",
    options: ["Cogsworth", "Lumière", "Mrs. Potts", "Chip"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the brave captain in 'Pirates of the Caribbean'?",
    answer: "Captain Jack Sparrow",
    options: [
      "Captain Jack Sparrow",
      "Will Turner",
      "Hector Barbossa",
      "Davy Jones",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which Disney character is known for his high-pitched voice and love for honey?",
    answer: "Winnie the Pooh",
    options: ["Winnie the Pooh", "Tigger", "Piglet", "Eeyore"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "In 'The Princess and the Frog,' what is the name of the trumpet-playing alligator?",
    answer: "Louis",
    options: ["Louis", "Ray", "Naveen", "Tiana"],
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the main antagonist in 'The Little Mermaid'?",
    answer: "Ursula",
    options: ["Ursula", "Ariel", "King Triton", "Sebastian"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which Disney character is a brave and determined toy cowboy in the 'Toy Story' franchise?",
    answer: "Woody",
    options: ["Woody", "Buzz Lightyear", "Jessie", "Rex"],
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the talking snowman in 'Frozen'?",
    answer: "Olaf",
    options: ["Olaf", "Sven", "Kristoff", "Hans"],
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the adventurous young boy in the movie 'Up'?",
    answer: "Russell",
    options: ["Russell", "Carl", "Dug", "Kevin"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which Disney character is a charismatic and mischievous pirate fox in 'Zootopia'?",
    answer: "Nick Wilde",
    options: ["Nick Wilde", "Judy Hopps", "Chief Bogo", "Flash"],
  },
  {
    question: "In Aladdin, what sort of pet is Rajah?",
    answer: "Tiger",
    options: ["Tiger", "Monkey", "Parrot", "Elephant"],
  },
];

export default qaArray;
